No, they are actually, as we speak, trying to overthrow the core law enforcement function
of the federal government.
Of course, this is, I think, what we're talking past each other.
When ICE officers have to street battle against Antifa, hand-to-hand combat every night to
come and go from their building, when they try to exit in a vehicle, when they are swarmed
and surrounded and they try to tip the vehicle over, when people bring weapons to an ICE
facility to try to engage in direct violent assault against ICE officers, what is the
purpose?
It is to prevent Immigration and Customs Enforcement from carrying out the mission the American
people elected them to do.
You make the case that these are terrorists, but in what we've seen thus far, the actual
incidents of people inciting violence and not responding to law enforcement attempting
to disperse them are not an open rebellion.
I mean, again, you make this characterization as though they're terrorists, and I do wonder
if it...